cnetturkiye.com 2012-06-28

# CBS Interactive Privacy Policy Highlights

**Scope of Privacy Policy**

| 

**Information Collected**  
  
CBS Interactive owns, operates, or provides access to, several interactive web sites and other interactive features that provide an authorized link to the [CBS Interactive Privacy Policy](http://cbsiprivacy.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/1268/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xMzQwOTA0OTc3L3NpZC9YRm81blBfaw== "CBS Interactive Privacy Policy") (collectively "CBS Interactive Web Sites"). This Privacy Policy, effective July 5, 2011, is guided by a core set of [Privacy Principles](http://cbsiprivacy.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/1266/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xMzQwOTA0OTc3L3NpZC9YRm81blBfaw== "Privacy Principles") and applies only to the [CBS Interactive Web Sites](http://www.cbsinteractive.com/our_brands.php).

» [Read more](http://cbsiprivacy.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/1268/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xMzQwOTA0OTc3L3NpZC9YRm81blBfaw==#Full01Scope "Read more")

| 

We collect a variety of information about you, including:

• Information you provide directly to a CBS Interactive Web Site.

• Information about your computer and browsing activities on the Web Sites, including through [cookies, web beacons, and other technologies](http://cbsiprivacy.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/1267/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xMzQwOTA0OTc3L3NpZC9YRm81blBfaw== "cookies, web beacons, and other technologies").

• Information about you from other sources where permitted by law.

» [Read more](http://cbsiprivacy.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/1268/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xMzQwOTA0OTc3L3NpZC9YRm81blBfaw==#Full02Collection "Read more")  
  
**Use of Information**

| 

**Disclosure of Information**  
  
We use the information we collect to:

• Provide the services you request.

• Tell you about offers we think you will value.

• Customize the content and advertising you see.

• Improve your experience on CBS Interactive Web Sites.

• As otherwise described to you at the point of collection or with your consent.

» [Read more](http://cbsiprivacy.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/1268/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xMzQwOTA0OTc3L3NpZC9YRm81blBfaw==#Full03Use "Read more")

| 

We may share your information:

• Where we have obtained your consent.

• With our third-party service providers.

• With business partners who sponsor a sweepstakes, contest, or promotion; or who jointly offer a service or feature with a CBS Interactive Web Site.

• Within the family of CBS Interactive Web Sites and other CBS businesses.

• If a CBS Interactive Web Site is sold to another company.

• To protect or defend the rights of CBS Interactive or our users.

• When required by law or public authorities.

» [Read more](http://cbsiprivacy.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/1268/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xMzQwOTA0OTc3L3NpZC9YRm81blBfaw==#Full04Disclosure "Read more")  
  
**Your Choices**

| 

**Other Information**  
  
• If you choose to share contact information with us, you will have the opportunity to update that information.

• You can stop the delivery of commercial email messages from a CBS Interactive Web Site or service by following the instructions in any such email you receive.

• You have choices about the collection and use of your information by third parties to display relevant advertisements, as described in our overview of [third-party online advertising](http://cbsiprivacy.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/1272/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xMzQwOTA0OTc3L3NpZC9YRm81blBfaw== "third-party online advertising").

• You also may choose to opt out of our use of data that we collect about your visits to our business partners’ sites to customize advertising that we serve. To opt out, visit the [CBS Interactive Business Partner Advertising Opt-Out](http://www.cbsinteractive.com/optout/setOptOut.php) page.

» [Read more](http://cbsiprivacy.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/1268/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xMzQwOTA0OTc3L3NpZC9YRm81blBfaw==#Full05Choices "Read more")

| 

• CBS Interactive is committed to working with you to obtain a fair resolution of any privacy concern.

• We have adopted commercially reasonable procedures to help protect your information, but please note that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

• For more information about our privacy practices, please review the full [CBS Interactive Privacy Policy](http://cbsiprivacy.custhelp.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/1268/session/L2F2LzEvdGltZS8xMzQwOTA0OTc3L3NpZC9YRm81blBfaw== "CBS Interactive Privacy Policy").  
  
**How to Contact Us**  
  
If you have questions regarding the CBS Interactive Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://cbsiprivacy.custhelp.com/app/ask).
